Hey, Ritchan.
りっちゃん おいっす
お～す
Hey there, Yui.
ああ… 暑い
So hot...
Huh? What's that you're looking at?
何 見てんの？
おもしろいもん見っけたぞ
I found something interesting. Here, check it out.
見てみ
Wow, what's with these pictures?
何これ？
この前 澪が見つけた段ボールに入ってたんだ
They were in a cardboard box that Mio found earlier.
They are pictures of a past Light Music Club.
昔の軽音部の写真みたい
Wow, these are amazing!
うわ～ すごいね
いつの時代のバンドだよって感じだよな
They've got that look every band has no matter when in history they played.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
えッ そ そうだね…
Say the word "band," and this used to be the only image that popped into my head.
バンドといえば こういうイメージしかなかった私って…
Chatting Now
CHATTING NOW
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
It's really noisy
Never Ending Girls' Talk
終業チャイムまで待てない
We can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
Even if we're late,
leaving early is a
No no!
精一杯Study After School
study
hard
We'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Our hearts won't stop thumping
Our thoughts are going on full throttle
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
We'll gather lots of data
and put it in a new type version
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
We have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
we can fly
If we cut our skirts
by 2 centimeters,
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Further than yesterday,
We'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
Jumping Now
Jumping
now
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never Ending
Girls' Life
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
We're looking
forward
to the daily
concert
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
Even if we
get up early,
going to bed
early is a
No no!
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
Shouting with all
W
e've
got
Hooray
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
It's splendid
Never Ending
Girls' Song
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
Our unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here we go!
歌えばShining After School
We'll
sing
for
you
After school
Maybe we can just try changing this a little bit.
ここ ちょっと変えてみるか
う～ん～
Ow!
痛て
What happened?
どうした？
I scraped the skin off my finger.
指の皮 むけちった
Wow, that looks painful.
うわッ 痛々しい
You, too, Mio! Look at my finger!
ほら～ 澪ちゃんも見て
Huh?
あれ
I'm not looking, I'm not listening, I'm not looking, I'm not listening...
見えない 聞こえない 見えない 聞こえない…
Am I hurt!
ああッ！
I've been practicing drums too much, the blisters on my hand broke open!
私もドラムの練習のしすぎで
手のマメ つぶれちゃった
Take a look! It's gross! Disgusting!
うりうり
うりうりうり
うりうり こら
Boo! Check it out! [???Dripping!]
こら 見てみ
こら マメが
Ritchan, do we have any adhesive bandages here?
りっちゃん ばんそうこうとか持ってない？
In your face!
澪 見て見て こら
Dah! It's near you!
こら 見て見て 澪ちゃん 見て見て あははッ
Don't mind me.
ごめんね
That's it!
I just need to borrow these music stands. Huh?
Look it! You!
こら 痛い痛い
ちょっと譜面台を… あら？
There!
Advisor!
Would the two of you mind carrying these notebooks for me?
２人でノートを持ってきてくれるかな
Thank you very much for all your help.
ありがとうございました
Ow!
痛～ッ
Huh?
あら？
The antiseptic is really stinging!
消毒 しみた～
I know. All right, hold your finger still just like that.
はいはい
指 そのまま固定しててね
What a tidy desk...
キレイな机
Done. There, that should do it.
はい これでいいわよ
Thanks for your help, Miss Yamanaka.
ありがとうございます
Let's see the others.
どれどれ
Um...
あの…
Well, you have a ways to go.
まだまだね
The way you skin is right now, it's going to peel off soon.
この分じゃ また すぐ皮むけるわよ
ええ～
Your skin will get tougher each time this happens and you'll become a better player in the process.
そうやって 何度もやってるうちに皮が硬くなって
弾けるようになるの
It's a guitarist's rite of passage.
誰もが通る道よ
う～ん そうなのか
Oh, it is?
Wait a sec! Did you used to play guitar, Miss Yamanaka?
あれ？ 先生 ギターやってたんですか？
Not me. But I have some friends who did.
ううん 昔 友達がね
Very good work today.
お疲れさまです
You, too.
じゃあね
See you later.
あッ はい
Yes.
Hey, would you like some tea?
先生 お茶いかがですか？
Yeah, thanks.
あッ どうも
What a nice teacher...
いい先生だな
ムギちゃ～ん
Mugi-chan!
えッ？！
Mugi-chan, is something the matter?
ムギちゃん どうかしたの？
えッ いえ…キレイだったなって思って
No, I, um... I was just thinking how pretty she was.
Oh, you mean Miss Yamanaka?
ああ さわ子先生ね
By the way, where have you been?
それより どこ行ってたの？
あッ うん 澪ちゃんに言われて
Well you see, I was asked by Mio to go find out if the Light Music Club could use the stage when we play at the school festival.
学園祭のステージを借りるための申請に行ってたんだけど
But I'm afraid they turned our request down because they said we weren't recognized as a legitimate club yet.
軽音部は まだちゃんとしたクラブって認められてないって
断られちゃった
Oh, that's nice.
ああ～ そっか～
えッ？
We're not recognized as a legitimate club?!
部として認められてないだって？
No, apparently we're not.
うん そうみたい
I thought, in order to be official, we just needed to have four members.
部員が４人集まったら大丈夫じゃなかったの？
Yeah, Yui, that's what I thought, too.
そのはずなんだけどな…
You know I was thinking, if we're not recognized as an official club,
ていうか クラブって認められてなかったのに
is it okay that we've been hogging the Music Room to ourselves?
音楽室 好き放題使ってよかったのかな
Look, nobody's said anything about it to us so far, so I'm sure it's okay. I think.
今まで何も言われなかったから
大丈夫だよ きっと…
それより どういう理由なのか聞きに行かないとな
More importantly, I'd better go and ask them why we're not recognized.
Yes, you should.
そうね
あれ そういや 澪は？
Hey, what happened to Mio?
Oh, if you're looking for Mio, she's still huddled in terror over there.
あッ 澪ちゃんなら
あそこで まだ おびえてる
Would you come back here?!
帰ってこ～い！
Greetings, all!
たのもう
I'm Club President!
部長は私
Oh, Yui?
あら 唯？
えッ 和ちゃん？
Nodoka-chan?
ええ～ 和ちゃんが 何でここに？
Nodoka-chan, what're you doing here?
What do you mean? I'm here because I'm on the student council.
何でって 生徒会だからだけど
えッ？
That's amazing! That's my Nodoka-chan!
すごいね さすが和ちゃんだよ
So you two are really childhood friends?
お前ら ホントに幼なじみ？
Well, sorry. But you don't seem to be on the list...
やっぱりリストには ないわね
Oh, no. You're kidding...
そんな…
No, don't tell me...
もしかして…
Ritchan! Does this raise any theories?
りっちゃん 何か心当たりが！？
Yes. What this appears to be--
うん 恐らく これは…
is a sinister plot by the student council to drive weak clubs to be disbanded!
弱小部を 廃部に追い込むための 生徒会の陰謀
I know you're really a pure-hearted person, Nodoka-chan! Please snap out of it!
和ちゃんは 本当は心がキレイな子
目を覚まして
What're are you talking about?
何の話？
Maybe you just didn't submit a club activities application form?
ていうか 部活申請用紙が出てないんじゃないの？
Club activities application?
部活申請用紙？
It's the first I've heard this form!
そんな話は聞いてないぞ
No, it's not!
聞いてるだろ！
Yes. That was back in spring...
そう あれは まだ春のこと
I'm Club President, so I'll fill it out!
私が部長だから 私が書く
Are you sure, Ritsu?
大丈夫か？
Excuse me, I brought a big pound cake with me today.
あの～ パウンドケーキ持ってきたんだけど
うは～ 食べようね
Let's dig in!
Hey, Ritsu, wait!
おい 律
I know, I know, Mio! I'll fill it out just as soon as we finish eating!
わ～かってるよ～
食べ終わったら すぐ書くって
I'll fill it out just as soon as we finish eating...
食べ終わったら すぐ書くって… 書くって… 書くって…
...finish eating...
I know this, this is all your fault! You're (here) putting things off!
やっぱり お前のせいか！
Oh, dear. Mio, it's not like she did it deliberately.
澪ちゃん りっちゃんも悪気があったわけじゃないし
You're too soft on her, Mugi!
ムギは甘いんだ！
Now, now, now, now, now, now, now...
まあまあ まあまあ まあまあ…
How do we put this?
何ていうか
I think you're a perfect fit for the Light Music Club, Yui.
軽音部って唯にぴったりだと思うわ
えッ？
Oh well, all right, Yui.
しょうがないわね～
私が 何とかしてあげるわ
I'll see what I can do for you.
えッ！
Well... You will?!
ホント！？
You will?!
Name, Light Music Club...
「軽音部」 と
Membership, four.
部員は４人
で…
Who's your advisor?
顧問は？
Advisor?
顧問？
You don't have one?
あんた達…
Sawako Yamanaka. Our fair school's music teacher.
山中さわ子
わが校の音楽教師である
As a result of her beautiful features and gentle demeanor,
そのキレイな顔立ちとやわらかな物腰で
she is popular with not only the student body, but also the school staff.
生徒だけでなく
教師の間でも人気が高い
Plus, her skill with instruments and her singing voice are remarkable.
さらに 楽器の腕前や歌声もすばらしく…
What?
あの
She is popular enough to have her own fan club.
ファンクラブが存在するほどの人気がある
What have you been going on about?
さっきから 何を言ってるの？
Hello, girls...
あなた達…
Teacher!
先生
What is it?
はい
Please agree to be the Light Music Club's advisor!
軽音部の顧問になってください
まだ 顧問いなかったんだ
Oh, I see, you don't have an advisor yet...
Miss Yamanaka, you're the only teacher that we can turn to.
先生しか 頼める人がいないんです
Oh, please do it.
お願いします
I'm so sorry. I wish that I could be your advisor, I really do.
ごめんなさい なってあげたいのはやまやまだけど
But I'm already the school band's advisor, so there's no way I could handle another.
私 吹奏楽部の顧問しているから 掛け持ちは ちょっと…
You're kidding...
そんな…
I really am sorry about this.
本当 ごめんなさいね
She's so desirable that she's been courted by countless men.
今まで声をかけてきた男は数知れず
Look, flattery isn't going to change anything!
だッ だから おだてても無理です
We won't take up any of your time!
時間なら取らせません
That's right, because we always practice on our own!
練習も自分達でやりますから
Just write your name here and give it your official stamp! Simple, huh?
ここに名前書いて ハンコ押すだけ
ねッ 簡単でしょ
J-Just wait a sec!
ちょ ちょっと…
Stare...
じ～
Miss Yamanaka, you graduated from here, didn't you?
先生 ここの卒業生ですよね？
Well, yes...
えッ ええ
We were looking through an old Light Music Club photo album earlier.
さっき 昔の軽音部のアルバム見てたんですけど
えッ！
Is something the matter with you?
どうかしたのか？
Um, so where is that album right now?
アッ アルバムは どこにあるの？
あッ
Well, it's in our club room.
部室ですけど
I see.
そう
Miss Yamanaka?
先生？
I would never have suspected that the last copy was being kept right here in the school.
まさか
最後の１冊が 学校に保管されているとは 思わなかったわ
うん？
That book contains a chapter of my bloody past that must never come to light.
あれは 決して人々に知られてはいけない 血塗られた歴史
決して目覚めさせてはいけない悪魔の子
A spawn of the devil that must never be awakened!
A forbidden book never to be seen!
見てはならない封印の書
A locked doorway that must never be opened!
開けてはならない禁断の扉
It's... It's... It's...
あれは あれは あれは…！
At last, it's over.
これで もう…
I knew it, that WAS you, Miss Yamanaka.
やっぱり 先生なんですね
You were this girl, weren't you?
ほら この人
Well played, if you've found me out.
よく わかったわね
It's true, I was once a Light Music Club member.
そうよ 私 軽音部にいたの
I never suspected.
いッ 意外でした
Does that mean that this is you?
じゃあ もしかして この声も
I've been waiting for you people to arrive! NOW DIE!
お前らがくるのを待っていた～
死ね～！
Stop it! I'm so ashamed!
やめて 恥ずかしい…
聞こえない 聞こえない…
I'm not listening, I'm not listening...
You're still dragging out that shtick?
まだ引きずってんのか
You were playing guitar, too?
あれ じゃあギターも
Hey, right! Play something!
そっか 弾いて 弾いて
えッ
Don't be shy!
まあまあ
ちょッ いや ダメ
I can't...
I can't!
ダメッ！
The characteristic weight of a Les Paul's mahogany and maple...
ああ… このマホガニーと メイプルのレスポール独特の重さ
This dulcet tone, full of sweetly distorted harmonics from its humbucker pickup...
このハムバッキング·ピックアップの甘くひずんだ
倍音の多い やわらかい音
Miss Yamanaka?
先生？
What the hell...
しゃ～ねえな
Her expression's changed!
目つき変わった！
She's shredding!
早弾き
She's tapping!
タッピング
She's Hendrix-ing!
歯ギター
Oh, no. My poor little guitar!
ああ… 私のギター
You sucks. You've been using the Music Room like it was yours!
おめ～ら
音楽室好きに使いすぎなんだよ！
We're so sorry!
ごッ ごめんなさい
In the first place, you four--
大体な！…
Did you all see that?
…今の見た？
Uh-huh.
うん…
I swore to myself I'd put on a ladylike front when I became a teacher...
先生のときは おしとやかキャラで通すって決めてたのに
Yeah, but Miss--
先生…
All of this began eight long years ago...
あれはもう ８年も前のこと
Why is she narrating all of a sudden?!
いきなり語り出した
I was...
私は…
けいおん！
I was... in love.
私は 恋をした
I love you...
好きです
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
But I like girls with more of a wild streak in them.
俺 もっとワイルドな女の子が好きなんだ
And so I made up my mind.
私は決心した
That I would become the girl of his dreams.
彼の好みの女性になろうと
I would be wilder.
もっとワイルドに
Wilder! Wilder! Ever wilder!
もっと もっと ワイルドに
More! More! More!
もっと もっと もっと
Wilder! Wilder! Wilder!
ワイルド ワイルド ワイルドに
I'll go out with you if you want!
つきあってやってもいいんだぜ
Sawako...
さわ子
You took it too far.
やりすぎ
I guess that's how it always ends, huh?
しょせん そんなものよね
You okay?
先生…
Please, spare me your words of comfort...
いいの なぐさめの言葉なんて
Teacher, please lift up your eyes.
先生 顔上げて
Oh, Ritchan!
りっちゃん
If you don't want this getting out, you will be our club advisor.
バラされたくなかったら顧問やってください
Ritchan, you're so resolute!
りっちゃん たくましい子
Mugi-chan?
ムギちゃん？
What's wrong?
どうした？
I don't know, it's Mugi-chan...
ムギちゃんが
Mugi!
ムギ！
Are you feeling okay? You look like you're kind of spacing out.
大丈夫？
何か ボーッとしてるよ
カゼ？
うッ ううん
うん？
And that's a brand-new original piece we've been working on.
て感じの オリジナルなんですけど
うん…
As our advisor, what's your opinion?
どうですか？ 顧問として
I have some concerns,
そうね 前ノリ 後ノリとか
such as the intro and outro, and the way your rhythm section is all over the place, and total lack of any cohesive hook.
リズムセクションがバラバラとか
いろいろ気になることはあるけど
But, don't you guys have a singer?
まず…ボーカルは いないの？
あッ！
Wait, you haven't written any lyrics yet, either, have you?
じゃあ まさか歌詞もまだ とか
Well, I guess we just...
え ええと…
You've got a lot of guts, thinking you could perform at the school festival in this state.
それで よく学園祭のステージに出ようなんて考えたわね
We're sorry, ma'am.
すみません
What have you been doing every time you've been hogging the music room?!
音楽室占領して今まで何やってたの！
ここは お茶を飲む場所じゃないのよ
It's not a place to sit around and sip tea!
We made her mad!
怒られた
For one thing!
大体ね！
Teacher!
先生！
Huh!
あん？！
W-Would you care for some yummy cake?
ケ… ケーキ いかがですか？
ええ～ッ
Yes, I would!
いただきます
She would?!
いただくんかい
Let's see...
え～と
はあ… 詞 先にすればよかった
We should've started with the lyrics first.
Mugi?
ムギか
"Now that Miss Yamanaka has become our advisor, my heart is pounding for some reason.
さわ子先生が顧問になってくれて
なんだかドキドキしています
Good luck with the lyrics."
歌詞作り頑張って
My heart is pounding?
「ドキドキ」…
Nah, no way...
まさかな
They're done?!
できた？！
Yeah, all done.
あ ああ…
Show us, show us!
見せて 見せて
えッ もう！？
Already?!
Yes, already!
いや もうって
私も見たいな
I would love to see them, too!
But... But I'm embarrassed to show them to you...
でッ でも やっぱり恥ずかしい
Come on, Mio-chan. No one is gonna laugh.
大丈夫だよ 笑ったりしないし
Yeah, yeah!
そうそう～
But I... Wait a minute!
でも… ああ 待って
We can't wait! If you brought them, that means you're ready to show them to us, right?!
待てない
持ってきたってことは見せるってことだろ
Mio, come on, please!
澪ちゃん お願い
You can give me a little peek! Just one little peek!
ちょ ちょっとだけ こそ～っと私に
No fair! If anybody's going to see them, I'm gonna be first!
あッ ずりい 見せんなら私が先だろ
Why you?
ええ～ 何で？
Why? Because I'm Club President, that's why!
なぜなら 私が部長だから
ぬッ… ならば
What? Then I'm Mio-chan's soulmate! So I can see them first, so there!
私は澪ちゃんの心の友だから
Well then, I'm Mio-chan's soulmate #2 and I get to see them next!
じゃあ私は 澪ちゃんの心の友 その２だから
You got a lot of gall, I am the place that Mio's soul calls home, right?
こしゃくな 私なんか澪の心のふるさとだぞ
Since when?
いつから そうなった？
Oh, I wonder how my granny who lives out in the country is doing?
田舎のおばあちゃん 元気かな
That's got nothing to do with this.
いや 今 関係ないから
Did I send mine a New Year's card last year?
あッ 去年 年賀状 出したっけ
Don't change the subject!
話をそらすな
Let's see the damn thing!
早く 見せんか～い！
Let me see!
どれどれ
"Every time I look at you, my heart"
"Starts thumping"
"The swaying memories are like marshmallows"
"Light and fluffy"
かッ かゆい
I'm all itchy all of this! Ow!
I'm all itchy!
破りたい
I think that considering how fast I did it, it turned out pretty well...
わッ 私としては いい感じに書けたと思うんだけど
Do you really think that it's no good?
やっぱ ダメかな
"No good" might be a little strong...
ダッ ダメっていうか
Yeah, more like it doesn't quite fit the image that we were trying to create.
そうそう ちょいイメージと違ったっていうか
C'mon, Yui, you haven't said anything. What do you think?
ほら 唯からも 何か言って
It was so awesome...
すごく いい
Seriously?!
マジで！？
I love these lyrics, I think they're just wonderful!
私は すごく好きだよ この歌詞
Y-You mean it?
ホ ホント？
Hey, what do you think about the lyrics, Mugi?
ムッ ムギは どう思う？
She's totally enchanted!
超 うっとりしてる～！
Mugi, you aren't seriously telling me that you like them.
まッ まさか ムギも気に入ったの？
I do...
はい
Uh, you think these lyrics work?
こういうの あり？
I do.
うん
Seriously?
ホントに？
???
イエス
For real?
マジで？
どんとこいです
Yes. Bring it on.
S-Sawako!
さわちゃん！
Sawako?
さわちゃん？
You think these lyrics are unworkable, right?
さわちゃんは この歌詞ないと思うよね？
Why, yes! I suppose they're not!
ええ… そッ そうね
See, I'm right.
だよね
Come on, you three, let's rethink our approach, okay?
三人とも もう少し考え直そうよ
Let's take a deep breath and--
まずは みんな落ち着いて…
Wait a minute...
待てよ
Maybe I can give my image a boost by saying I like this perky, sappy crap.
こういうキャピキャピした曲を好きって言ったほうが
私のイメージ 上がるかも
You're young at heart, Miss Yamanaka!
先生 若いですね
That's our Miss Yamanaka!
さすが さわ子先生
It's Miss Yamanaka or no one!
もう さわ子先生っきゃない
Yamanaka! Yamanaka! Yamanaka! Yamanaka!
さわ子 さわ子 さわ子…
You know now that I think about it, I guess I really like this lyrics, too!
わッ 私も この曲 好きかも～
Say what?!
あれ！？
Well, I suppose we're going with these lyrics, then.
それじゃあ もう この歌詞でいくか
Yay!
Isn't this wonderful, Mio-chan?
よかったね 澪ちゃん
Um, yeah...
ああ… うん
That means, we'll be going with Mio on vocals.
じゃあ 澪がボーカルってことで
えッ
N-No, I couldn't!
わッ 私は無理だよ
Why not?
何で？
Uh, well, I, uh... Because I...
だッ だって…
だって…こんな恥ずかしい歌詞なんか 歌えないよ
Because I can't sing such embarrassing lyrics, that's why!
Hey, you wrote 'em, lady!
おい 作者
This is gonna be a problem.
困ったわね
Well, I guess that leaves us with...
うん… 澪がダメとなると
Mugi, wanna try?
ムギ やってみる？
えッ
I would. But I already have my hands full just managing the keyboard.
私は キーボードで精いっぱいだし
Um. Okay, then...
そっか… じゃあ
I guess not.
だよね
Yui, you wanna try?
…唯 やってみるか？
What? You're asking me?!
えッ 私？
でも 歌 そんなにうまくないし
But I'm not really a good singer, you know, so I don't know if I'd be the best choice for us, so I'm not sure if I should even try to do it.
私で務まるか どうかわかんないっていうか…
Never mind, then.
じゃあ いいや
I'm sorry, I lied! I'll sing! I wanna sing! You gotta let me try it!
ごめん ウソ 歌う
歌いたいです
Okay then, sing something.
それじゃあ 歌ってみよっか
Roger!
ラジャー
Every time I look at you, my heart—
キミを見てると いつもハート…
Hold it, hold it!
ちょっと ちょっと
You'll have to sing while you're playing the guitar!
ギター弾きながら歌わないと
Oh yeah, you're right. I totally forgot.
あッ そっか 忘れてた
Oh, geez.
おいおい
えっと…
Okay...
This time she's forgetting to sing when she plays!
…今度は歌 忘れてる
I can't sing and play guitar at the same time! I can't...
ギターを弾きながら歌が歌えない
I guess I have no choice. I'll have to give you special training.
仕方ないわね
先生が特訓してあげる
Really?
先生
First thing, I'm gonna show you is how to Hendrix...
それじゃあ まず歯ギターのやり方は…
That's all right.
それはいいです
Okay, do your best and try to keep up with me!
じゃあ 振り落とされないようについてきなさいよ
Roger!
ラジャー
Ritsu...
律
What is it?
何？
ムギってさ
You don't think that Mugi has a thing for Miss Yamanaka, do you?
もしかしてさわ子先生のこと…
Come again?
何？
What I'm trying to ask is, think she's got a crush on her?
いや だから
さわ子先生をさ
What, seriously?
えッ マジで
ムギ さわ子先生のこと好きなのか？
Mugi! I was wondering, do you like Miss Yamanaka?
Hey, Ritsu!
あッ ちょッ…
You moron!
バカ！
えッ？
ああ いえ
Oh, no. I was just... I was thinking how nice it is when it's just girls hanging out.
ただ女の子同士っていいなって
What? No way!
えッ まさか…
Oh well, good for you.
何だ よかった
Wait! So you're okay with it?
えッ いいのかよ
If the people involved are happy, that's all that really matters, right?
本人達がよければいいんじゃないでしょうか
Well, um...
えっと ああ… うん？
あッ 何を言ってるんだ？
What are we talking about here?
All right, then. Yui will be providing vocals, and the set list will be "Fuwa Fuwa Time."
ええと ボーカルが唯で 曲目が「ふわふわタイム」と
Okay, I'll get in touch with you again once your time slot has been assigned.
ＯＫ じゃあ 出演時間決まったらまた連絡するね
Thank goodness and thank you for coming here in person to tell us.
よかった
わざわざ きてもらってありがとう
It's all part of a student council member's duties.
これも生徒会の仕事だから
でも ホントに唯で大丈夫なの？
But, are you really sure you wanna go with Yui on the vocals?
先週から放課後 さわ子先生の家で特訓してるからな
She's been getting intensive lessons from Miss Yamanaka after school since last week.
We think that she'll have her whipped into shape in time.
たぶん 間に合うんじゃないかと
Sorry to keep you waiting.
待たせたわね
She's perfect.
完ぺきよ
Now, Yui, girl. Show 'em what you've got!
さあ唯ちゃん 見せてあげなさい
She's awesome!
すげ～
She's a lot of better!
上達している
Her face is full of confidence!
自信に満ちあふれた表情
Every time I look at you, my heart starts thumping...
キミを見てると いつもハートＤＯＫＩ★ＤＯＫＩ…
えへッ
I made her practice too much!
練習させすぎちゃった
I threw my voice out!
声かれちゃった
Knock off the cutesy act!
カワイ子ぶってもダメだ！
You're kidding... Who will do the vocals, then?
そんな…
じゃあボーカルは？
All changes must be in by the end of the day.
変更するなら今日中よ
What?! You are not serious!
えッ そうなのか？
だとすると…
In that case...
うん？
えッ？！
You're right. Mio is the only other person who knows the lyrics.
そうね 澪ちゃんなら 歌詞 覚えてるだろうし
Yeah, 'cause she's the one who came up with them.
歌詞作った本人だしな
がんばってね 澪ちゃん
I know you can do it, Mio.
ハスキー唯からも お願い
Do it for Husky Voiced Yui!
ああッ…
Oh, Mio!
おおいッ！
Mio, what's the matter?!
澪ちゃん？
Pull yourself together!
しっかりしろ～
There's only three days 'til we go on!
本番まで あと３日
Please
don't say
"you are
lazy,"
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
I am
actually
crazy
だって本当はcrazy
The swans
are actually
白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the easy way out
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Capable
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
Ritsu, don't you think we should get some practicing before we go on?
ねえ 律
本番前の練習 やっておかない？
I'm sorry, but I can't right now.
あッ ごめん 今 無理
Well, you still have a fair amount of time until then. Don't you wanna use the time to practice?
じゃあ まだ結構時間あるし
練習しておきたいんじゃないの？
She's right! Let's practice!
そうだ 練習だ
何もなかった
Pretend that didn't happen. That didn't happen.
何もなかったんだ
Today's the day of the performance! Let's try and practice as much as we can!
今日本番だろ
めいっぱい練習しておこうよ
Let's practice!
練習しよう
We're gonna practice, huh?
練習か…
School Festival!